Guide to the Board of Trustees Records, 1860-ongoing UA.02.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Duke University, 1923-2010
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1923-1985
    - November 7, 2003-June 18, 2004 (Volume 76)
    - August 27-November 4, 2004 (Volume 77)
    - January 14-June 17, 2005 (Volume 78)
    - August 26-November 4, 2005 (Volume 79)
    - January 20-June 17, 2006 (Volume 80)
    - August 25-November 17, 2006 (Volume 81)
    - January 12-June 15, 2007 (Volume 82)
    - July 20-December 17, 2007 (Volume 83)
    - January 18-June 13, 2008 (Volume 84)
    - September 15-November 7, 2008 (Volume 85)
    - January 15-June 19, 2009 (Volume 86)
    - July 24-November 6, 2009 (Volume 87)
    - January 15-March 26, 2010 (Volume 88)
    - June 18-November 5, 2010 (Volume 89)
    - Duplicate Minutes, 1946-1979
      - June 26, 1946-December 1, 1954 (Box 17)
      - February 23, 1955-November 25, 1959 (Box 17)
      - February 24, 1960-December 12, 1965 (Box 17)
      - January 21, 1966-December 6, 1968 (Box 17)
      - January 17, 1969-December 11, 1970 (Box 17)
      - January 22, 1971-December 10, 1971 (Box 18)
      - January 14, 1972-December 7, 1973 (Box 18)
      - January 18, 1974-November 7, 1975 (Box 18)
      - January 16, 1976-November 4, 1977 (Box 18)
      - January 13, 1978-March 30, 1979 (Box 18)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, electronic copies, 1979-2019 (Digital-materials UA02010001-SET-0001)
  - Board of Trustees General Records, 1922-1961
    The Board of Trustees General Records subseries contains both topical and yearly files on matters related to the Board and its meetings.
    - Topics, 1922-1961 (Box 6)
      The Topics subseries contains a variety of materials on issues of relevance to the Board of Trustees. The Topics have been placed in alphabetical order. Please note that the Topics subseries in the Trinity College series contains a folder called "Trustee lists" that has information about trustees up through 1948.
      - Administrative Committee, 1934 (Box 6)
      - Bylaws--"Latest," 1935 (Box 6)
      - Charter/Bylaws, circa 1935 (Box 6)
      - Correspondence concerning a successor to President Few, October 1940-February 1941 (Box 6)
      - Curriculum Study, 1939 (Box 6)
      - Gross-Edens Affair, February 1960-April 1960 (Box 6)
      - Institute for Research in the Sciences of Man, 1931-1939 (Box 6)
      - International Studies, 1935 (Box 6)
      - Library, 1932 (Box 6)
      - Memorials, circa 1925-1936 (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous materials, circa 1925-1945 (Box 6)
      - Petition by Women Students to Name Auditorium on Woman's College after Dean Baldwin, circa 1930 (Box 6)
      - Philosophy Department, 1938 (Box 6)
      - Physics, 1936 (Box 6)
      - Psychology Department, 1938 (Box 6)
      - Ring Petition, 1932 (Box 6)
      - School of Medicine and School of Nursing Announcements, circa 1929-1930 (Box 6)
      - Student Letters to Trustees regarding integration, 1956-1961 (Box 6)
      - Teaching Load, circa 1934 (Box 6)
      - "A Tour of Inspection" (motion picture), 1934 (Box 6)
      - Transfer of Title (Extracts from Minutes), 1922-1938 (Box 6)
      - Widgery, Alban G. - RESTRICTED, circa 1933-1934 (Box 6)
    - Yearly Files, 1924-1960
      Yearly Files include agendas, correspondence, reports, and other materials used before, during, and after meetings of the Board of Trustees. Materials are arranged chronologically. Materials that were used in preparation for, during, or following a meeting have been retained together in folders labeled with the meeting date.
      - December 29, 1924 meeting (Box 6)
      - 1925 (Box 8)
      - 1926 (Box 8)
      - 1927 (Box 8)
      - 1928 (Box 8)
      - 1929 (Box 8)
      - 1930 (Box 8)
      - 1931 (Box 8)
      - June 1931 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1932 (Box 8)
      - January 26, 1932 Joint Meeting of the Duke Endowment and Duke University (Box 8)
      - 1933 (Box 8)
      - June 5, 1933 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1934 (Box 8)
      - February 28, 1934 meeting (Box 8)
      - June 4, 1934 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1935 (Box 8)
      - March 27, 1935 meeting (Box 8)
      - June 1, 1935 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1936 (Box 8)
      - January 29, 1936 meeting (Box 8)
      - June 6, 1936 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1937 (Box 8)
      - January 27, 1937 meeting (Box 8)
      - May 1937-June 1937 (Box 8)
      - June 5, 1937 meeting (Box 8)
      - February 2, 1938 meeting (Box 8)
      - 1939 (Box 8)
      - March 1, 1939 meeting (Box 8)
      - June 3, 1939 meeting (Box 8)
      - January 31, 1940 meeting (Box 8)
      - June 1, 1940 meeting (Box 8)
      - December 1940-April 1941 (Box 8)
      - May 1941-June 1941 (Box 8)
      - January 1942-April 1942 (Box 9)
      - May 1942-July 1942 (Box 9)
      - October 1942-June 1943 (Box 9)
      - December 1943-June 1944 (Box 9)
      - December 1944-June 1945 (Box 9)
      - April 1946-June 1946 (Box 9)
      - February 26, 1947 meeting (Box 9)
      - May 31, 1947 meeting (Box 9)
      - November 26, 1947 meeting (Box 9)
      - June 4, 1948 meeting (Box 9)
      - November 19, 1948 meeting (Box 9)
      - June 4, 1949 meeting (Box 9)
      - December 10, 1949 meeting (Box 9)
      - June 3, 1950 meeting (Box 9)
      - June 2, 1951 meeting (Box 9)
      - February 27, 1952 meeting (Box 9)
      - May 31, 1952 meeting (Box 9)
      - February 25, 1953 meeting (Box 9)
      - May 30, 1953 meeting (Box 9)
      - February 24, 1954 meeting (Box 9)
      - June 5, 1954 meeting (Box 10)
      - February 23, 1955 meeting (Box 10)
      - June 4, 1955 meeting (Box 10)
      - February 29, 1956 meeting (Box 10)
      - June 2, 1956 meeting (Box 10)
      - February 27, 1957 meeting (Box 10)
      - June 1, 1957 meeting (Box 10)
      - February 26, 1958 meeting (Box 10)
      - May 31, 1958 meeting (Box 10)
      - February 25, 1959 meeting (Box 10)
      - June 6, 1959 meeting (Box 10)
      - March 23, 1960 meeting (Box 10)
      - April 21, 1960 meeting (Box 10)
      - June 4, 1960 meeting (Box 10)
    - Board of Trustees general records, electronic files, 1990-2008 (Digital-materials UA02010001-SET-0001)
  - Executive Committee General Records, 1930-1959
    Executive Committee General Records include agendas, correspondence, reports, and other materials used before, during, and after meetings of the Executive Committee. Materials are arranged chronologically. Materials that were used in preparation for, during, or following a meeting have been retained together in folders labeled with the meeting date.
    - 1930 (Box 10)
    - 1932 (Box 10)
    - January 1934 and March 1934 meetings (Box 10)
    - March 28, 1934 meeting (Box 10)
    - August 29, 1934 meeting (Box 10)
    - October 6, 1934 meeting (Box 10)
    - December 19, 1934 meeting (Box 10)
    - 1935 (Box 10)
    - January 30, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - February 14, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - April 17, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - May 29, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - July 1935-August 1935 (Box 10)
    - September 4, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - September 25, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - October 30, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - November 27, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - December 18, 1935 meeting (Box 10)
    - January 28, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - February 26, 1936 and March 26, 1936 meetings (Box 10)
    - April 1, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - May 27, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - June 26, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - August 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - September 26, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - October 28, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - December 9, 1936 meeting (Box 10)
    - January 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - February 24, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - March 31, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - April 23, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - May 26, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - June 23, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - July 28, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - September 8, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - October 27, 1937 meeting (Box 10)
    - December 22, 1937 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 23, 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - April 4, 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - May 25, 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - July 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 28, 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - December 10, 1938 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 1, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - March 1, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - March 29, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 3, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 28, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - August 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 29, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 29, 1939 meeting (Box 11)
    - January 30, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 28, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - May 1, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 1, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 26, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 25, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - October 18, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 2, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 27, 1940 meeting (Box 11)
    - December 1940-May 1941 (Box 11)
    - June 1941 (Box 11)
    - September 1941-December 1941 (Box 11)
    - January 1942-June 1942 (Box 11)
    - September 1942-December 1942 (Box 11)
    - February 1943-April 1943 (Box 11)
    - August 1943-December 1943 (Box 11)
    - March 1, 1944 meeting (Box 11)
    - April 26, 1944 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 27, 1944 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 29, 1944 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 28, 1945 meeting (Box 11)
    - April 25, 1945 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 27, 1945 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 26, 1945 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 28, 1945 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 27, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - May 1, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 26, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - July 12, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - September 25, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 27, 1946 meeting (Box 11)
    - April 30, 1947 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 25, 1947 meeting (Box 11)
    - October 1, 1947 meeting (Box 11)
    - November 26, 1947 meeting (Box 11)
    - January 16, 1948 meeting (Box 11)
    - February 25, 1948 meeting (Box 11)
    - April 28, 1948 meeting (Box 11)
    - June 5, 1948 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 30, 1948 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 29, 1948 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 19, 1948 meeting (Box 12)
    - December 1, 1948 meeting (Box 12)
    - January 8, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 23, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 27, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 4, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 29, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 30, 1949 and December 10, 1949 meeting (Box 12)
    - January 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - March 1, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 26, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 3, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 28, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 27, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 27, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 29, 1950 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 28, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 25, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - May 31, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 2, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 27, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 26, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 28, 1951 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 27, 1952 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 30, 1952 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 25, 1952 meeting (Box 12)
    - October 1, 1952 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 26, 1952 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 25, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 29, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - May 30, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - July 1, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 24, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 25, 1953 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 23, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 28, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 5, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 30, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 23, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - December 1, 1954 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 23, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 27, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 3, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 29, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - September 28, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - November 30, 1955 meeting (Box 12)
    - February 28, 1956 meeting (Box 12)
    - April 25, 1956 meeting (Box 12)
    - June 1, 1956 meeting (Box 13)
    - June 27, 1956 meeting (Box 13)
    - September 26, 1956 meeting (Box 13)
    - November 28, 1956 meeting (Box 13)
    - February 27, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - May 1, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - May 31, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - June 26, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - September 25, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - November 27, 1957 meeting (Box 13)
    - February 25, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - March 31, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - April 30, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - May 31, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - June 25, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - October 1, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - November 26, 1958 meeting (Box 13)
    - February 25, 1959 meeting (Box 13)
    - April 29, 1959 meeting (Box 13)
    - June 5, 1959 meeting (Box 13)
  - Reports, 1948-1960
    Reports include both those produced by the Board of Trustees and those presented to the Board by outside parties. Materials are arranged chronologically.
    - A Report on the Financial Needs and Resources of Duke University, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Report on Examiniation of Accounts, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Report on Organization and Management, 1960
      - Summary (Box 13)
      - Volume 1 (Box 13)
      - Volume 2 (Box 13)
  - Financial Records, 1923-1959
    The Budget subseries contains yearly budget information, financial reports, endowment and investment reports, studies, audits, and other information related to the financial administration of Duke University. Materials are arranged chronologically.
    - Investment Holdings, General Correspondence, 1923-1929 (Box 13)
    - Funds, Miscellaneous, 1925-1939 (Box 13)
    - Budget, circa 1925-1930 (Box 13)
    - Investment Holdings, General Correspondence, 1929-1937 (Box 13)
    - Budget, 1930 (Box 13)
    - Budget, 1931-1932 (non-medical) (Box 13)
    - Funds, Amelie McAlister Upshur, 1934-1936 (Box 14)
    - Budget
      - 1935-1936 (Box 14)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 14)
      - 1937-1938 (New and Promotions, Salaries) (Box 14)
    - Duke University investments and their indivisible interest in investments of the Duke Endowment, May 31, 1940 (Box 14)
    - Budget income and expenditure statements, 1942-1948 (Box 14)
    - The Duke Endowment--securities held for Duke University, 1943-1949 (Box 14)
    - Financial Reports, 1945-1948 (Box 14)
    - Duke Endowment, 1945-1950 (Box 14)
    - Analysis of Duke University investments, June 30, 1945-December 31, 1946 (Box 14)
    - Analysis of Duke University investments, January 1, 1947-December 31, 1948 (Box 14)
    - Stores study, 1945-1947 (Box 14)
    - Study of Retail Stores Operations at Duke University, 1945-1947 (Box 14)
    - Duke University construction, 1945-1950 (Box 14)
    - Duke University Development Program Operating Plan, 1948 (Box 14)
    - Trend of Income and Expenses, 1948-1949 (Box 14)
    - Budgets, 1949-1951 (Box 14)
    - Duke University Audit, Comments, 1950 (Box 14)
    - Elizabeth P. Hanes Building Fund and Annuity Fund, 1950 (Box 14)
    - Memorandum for IBM equipment, circa 1950-1953 (Box 14)
    - Duke University Athletic Council, 1950-1953 (Box 14)
    - Consolidated Balance Sheets, etc., 1959 (Box 14)
  - Committees, circa 1936-1953
    Committees are comprised of Board of Trustees members. Committees represented here (for only brief periods of time each) include the Audit Committee, the Academic Affairs Committee, the Buildings and Grounds Committee, the Business and Finance Committee, the Committee on Honorary Degrees, the Faculty, Grad, and Professional School Committee, the Human Resources Committee, the Institutioal Advancement Committee, the Medical Center Affairs Committee, the Student Affairs Committee, and the Undergraduate Affairs Committee.
    - Committee on Honorary Degrees
      - Biographies (Box 14)
      - Correspondence
        - 1936-1943 (Box 14)
        - April 1944-December 1947 (Box 14)
        - January 1948-February 1949, undated (Box 14)
        - 1949-1950 (Box 14)
        - 1949-1952 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence and biographies, 1949-1952 (Box 14)
      - Member correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 14)
      - Meeting, December 1951 (Box 15)
      - Nominations, biographies, and correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 15)
      - Nominations, biographies, and correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 15)
      - Recommendations, 1940-1950 (Box 15)
    - Committees, 2005-2007 (Digital-materials UA02010001-SET-0001)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes materials from the Audit Committee, the Academic Affairs Committee, the Buildings and Grounds Committee, the Business and Finance Committee, the Faculty, Grad, and Professional School Committee, the Human Resources Committee, the Institutioal Advancement Committee, the Medical Center Affairs Committee, the Student Affairs Committee, and the Undergraduate Affairs Committee.
- Duke University Unprocessed Materials, 1959-2004
  Unprocessed Materials are primarily those less than 50 years old. A box-level guide is provided for these materials, but patrons wishing to use them must receive special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees. These materials are arranged into three subseries: Meeting Files, Committee Files, and Other Materials.
  - Meeting Files, 1959-2004
    The Meeting Files subseries is comprised of supplementary materials related to meetings of the entire Board of Trustees as well as meetings of the Executive Committee. The description of each box specifies whether it contains only Board of Trustees materials, only Executive Committee materials, or both. Boxes are arranged in chronological order.
    - Executive Committee meeting files, July 1, 1959-February 28, 1963 (Box 19)
    - Board of Trustees meeting files, 1961-1965 (Box 20)
    - Executive Committee meeting files, January 21, 1963-December 10, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 21, 1966-March 2, 1967 (Box 22)
      Also includes stenographer's notebooks.
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 6, 1967-February 29, 1968 (Box 23)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, March 1, 1968-March 29, 1969 (Box 24)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, May 2, 1969-December 13, 1969 (Box 25)
      Also includes "old trustee mailing lists" dating from 1964 to 1975.
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 16, 1970-April 2, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 30, 1971-June 9, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 25, 1972-September 21, 1973 (Box 28)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, September 21, 1973-June 14, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 23, 1974-July 18, 1975, Accession Number A83-17 (Box 30)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 22, 1975-July 16, 1976, Accession Number A83-17 (Box 31)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 20, 1976-July 15, 1977, Accession Number A83-17 (Box 32)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, September 23, 1977-June 29, 1978, Accession Number A85-90 (Box 33)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, July 14, 1978-May 5, 1979, Accession Number A85-90 (Box 34)
    - 1978 Board of Trustees meeting files (Box 35)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, June 8, 1979-May 10, 1980, Accession Number A85-90 (Box 36)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, June 13, 1980-September 26, 1981, Accession Number A89-16 (Box 37)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, September 26, 1981-December 11, 1982, Accession Number A89-16 (Box 38)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 14, 1983-December 10, 1983, Accession Number A89-112 (Box 39)
      Box also includes Nixon Library CANDL file, naming of rooms file, and Bylaws of Highland Hospital Medical Staff file.
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 20, 1984-April 5, 1985, Accession Number A89-112 (Box 40)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, May 3, 1985-June 13, 1986, Accession Number A89-112 (Box 41)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 21, 1986-May 9, 1987, Accession Number A90-106 (Box 42)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, June 12, 1987-May 7, 1988, Accession Number A90-106 (Box 43)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, June 10, 1988-February 25, 1989, Accession Numbers A91-79, A92-16 (Box 44)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 7, 1989-December 9, 1989, Accession Number A92-16 (Box 45)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 23, 1990-October 6, 1990, Accession Number A93-3 (Box 46)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, October 5, 1990-December 8, 1990, Accession Number A93-3 (Box 47)
      Box also includes a few reports.
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 22, 1991-August 23, 1991, Accession Number A93-81 (Box 48)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, September 27, 1991-December 7, 1991, Accession Number A93-81 (Box 49)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 9, 1992-June 12, 1992, Accession Number A93-135 (Box 50)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 21, 1992-December 12, 1992, Accession Number A94-17 (Box 51)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 15, 1993-May 15, 1993, Accession Numbers A94-82, A95-44 (Box 52)
    - Board of Trustees meeting files, May 14, 1993-December 11, 1993, Accession Numbers A94-82, A95-44 (Box 53)
    - Executive Committee meeting files, June 11, 1993-January 14, 1994, Accession Number A95-25 (Box 54)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 25, 1994-June 10, 1994, Accession Number A95-59 (Box 55)
    - Executive Committee meeting files, July 27, 1994-January 13, 1995, Accession Number A96-15 (Box 56)
    - Board of Trustees meeting files, September 30, 1994-December 10, 1994, Accession Number A96-15 (Box 57)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, December 9, 1994-May 13, 1995, Accession Numbers A96-15, A96-127 (Box 58)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, January 13, 1995-September 30, 1995, Accession Numbers A96-15, A96-94, A97-24 (Box 59)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, September 29, 1995-December 9, 1995, Accession Number A97-24 (Box 60)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 23, 1996-July 19, 1996, Accession Number A97-54 (Box 61)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 23, 1996-March 1, 1997, Accession Number A98-70 (Box 62)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 28, 1997-June 13, 1997, Accession Number A98-70 (Box 63)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 22, 1997-March 1, 1998, Accession Number A99-73 (Box 64)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, February 27, 1998-1999, Accession Number A99-73 (Box 65)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, October 2, 1998-February 27, 1999, Accession Number A2000-53 (Box 66)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, April 9, 1999-June 11, 1999, Accession Numbers A2000-53, A2001-65 (Box 67)
    - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee meeting files, August 20, 1999-August 25, 2000, Accession Number A2001-65 (Box 68)